<root>
	<current>
		<user>
			<new summary="Initial release">Initial release</new>

			<bug summary="Selection and text input form stays on top in Internet Explorer 6">
				With Internet Explorer 6, selection and text input form will in a window remain above other windows even if the window is below others.
				This is the browser's fault and not likely to be fixed.
				To overcome this problem, upgrading Internet Explorer or using another browser is necessary.
			</bug>

			<bug summary="Some edge of the window cannot be used to drag windows in Internet Explorer 6.">
				With Internet Explorer 6, by clicking on some edge of a window to drag the window does not work.
				This is likely to be a bug in the browser's rendering and a workaround is not yet thought out.
				To overcome this problem, upgrading Internet Explorer or using another browser is necessary.
			</bug>

			<bug summary="Resizing a window is sometimes inaccurate on Firefox/Opera/Konqueror">
				When resizing a window, the end result is inaccurate under certain conditions for those browsers.
				This is hard to fix difference on the rendering implementations on the browsers but a workaround is being planned.
			</bug>

			<bug summary="Slow performance under certain wallpapers with Firefox in some cases">
				When a wallpaper is set with resizing but without streching and without centering, the performance can get degraded under Firefox under some cases.
				This is a problem of the browser and not likely to be fixed until the browser is fixed.
				Try other combinations of background options to work around the problem.
			</bug>
		</user>
	</current>

	<plan>
		<user>
			<change summary="Allow changing the window colors" priority="3">
				Allow changing the color of windows to custom colors.
			</change>

			<change summary="Add more language translations" priority="3">
				Add more language translations to the system. Other applications also need to be translated.
			</change>

			<new summary="Contextual menu" priority="4">
				Have contextual menu by right clicking the screen for easier navigation.
			</new>

			<new summary="Data export feature" priority="3">
				Add data export feature on applications so that the data stored can be downloaded by the user.
			</new>

			<new summary="Test HTML5" priority="5">
				Test the new HTML5 use possibility for browsers supporting it.
			</new>

			<new summary="Mobile device support" priority="3">
				Make the system usable against mobile devices such as smart phones.
			</new>

			<fix summary="Offline stability" priority="3">
				Stabilize the system when the connection is down.
			</fix>
		</user>

		<dev>
			<change summary="Add more server side languages" priority="5">
				Add more supported languages to run on the server side.
				Possible candidates so far are Ruby, Python and Perl.
			</change>

			<change summary="Use sprite for images" priority="2">
				Combine several images together to have less network load.
			</change>
		</dev>
	</plan>
</root>
